<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    <category>
        <pattern>hi</pattern>
        <template>Welcome! My name is Max, and I am a career guidance chatbot! Let's start with your strenghts to help decide a Computer Science Career path for you. Type "start" to begin.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>start</pattern>
        <template>
            Let's begin! Which of the following words best describes you?
            <button>
                <text>Leader</text>
                <postback>leadership</postback>
            </button>
            <button>
                <text>Detail-oriented</text>
                <postback>detail</postback>
            </button>
            <button>
                <text>Artistic</text>
                <postback>artistic</postback>
            </button>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>leadership</pattern>
        <template>Project Manager is a great career choice for people who are strong leaders. 
        If you like to work with people and lead projects from start to finish then 
        you should consider a career in project management!</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>detail</pattern>
        <template>
            Which sounds more appealing to you?
            <button>
                <text>Identify and manage risks for a company's networks and preventing security breaches.</text>
                <postback>security</postback>
            </button>
            <button>
                <text>Create and test software that successfully mimicks human intelligence</text>
                <postback>ai</postback>
            </button>
        </template>
    </category>
    
    
    <category>
        <pattern>security</pattern>
        <template>IT Security Analyst is a great career choice for detail-oriented professionals. As a security analyst you will monitor and manage risks on a network,
        implement firewalls and other protections, and help people steer clear of malicious websites and other attacks.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>ai</pattern>
        <template>AI Engineer is a great career choice for individuals who are interested and excited about the current leaps in technology. As an AI engineer you will create 
        and train software with the intention of having software mimick human intelligence.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>artistic</pattern>
        <template>
            Which sounds more appealing to you?
            <button>
                <text>Create responsive, eye-catching designs for computer software user interfaces</text>
                <postback>ux</postback>
            </button>
            <button>
                <text>Tell compelling stories through use of computer graphics</text>
                <postback>games</postback>
            </button>
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>ux</pattern>
        <template>UX Designer is a great career choice for technically minded people who have an eye for design! As a UX designer you will create user facing designs
        for different types of software.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>games</pattern>
        <template>Video Game Developer is a great career choice for artisitc individuals who love telling stories. As a video game developer, you will design and create video games
        utilizing skills in computer graphics.</template>
    </category>
    
    
    
  <category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>I have no answer for that. Please type "hi" to find a great career fit!</template>
  </category>
</aiml>
